Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
Excuse me, something
is happening...
What the...?
It's him!
Get him up!
Why the hell are you so weak?
- Pilot, get him to the stairs!
- Come on!
Hurry!
- Move your feet!
- He's shell-shocked!
Freaking Astronomer,
it's impossible to understand.
Come on!
Hurry!
Just follow us,
understand?
Come on, jump!
Hurry!
Let's go!
Come on.
That's it.
We're done for.
Told you so.
Told you...
Don't...
We're out of time!
Off you go.
I can't carry you any longer.
Wait!
Who the hell are you?
Where are we going?
You wanna stay?
- What happened to me?
- How would I know?
Car accident
or maybe an OD...
Am I dead?
Coma.
You mean this is all
a dream?
Memories.
- Whose?
- Everyone who's in a coma.
Everyone who's in a coma
comes to the same place-- here.
Our brain creates
a field of memories.
When in a coma, it switches off
and adjusts to this field.
Like how a radio
picks up signals. Look.
Buildings, objects, people...
Whatever we remember is here.
Whatever we don't remember
simply doesn't exist.
So there you have it.
Memories...
It doesn't makes sense.
What about the ones that...
They aren't people. I'm
telling you, they're memories.
Ok, and what about
those black creatures?
Are those memories, too?
Hold on!
Hold on.
Soldier Fly!
Are you going to secure
the perimeter or should I?
I already did.
Do it again then.
Listen,
where are we going anyway?
- Wait, does it fly?
- Get in already.
It's a wormhole.
That happens sometimes.
Someone remembered the bus
near the building
and someone else
in the field.
The memories are mixed up.
Where is he?
Where is Pilot?
He had to distract the Reaper
with a whistle.
We wouldn't have
gotten out otherwise.
- You left... You left him?!
- Hey!
Didn't I tell you how
dangerous that district is?
And that map was bullshit.
There wasn't enough time,
I told you.
You were rushing me!
Everything has changed there.
Why did we have to go there
in the first place?
I'm absolutely sure...
...it was worth it.
Fly, show him around.
And get him settled in upstairs.
Let's go.
The show's over!
Chop-chop!
Tank, what's up
with the trail?
Are you waiting for the Reapers
to come over?
Blow it up already!
But we're running low
on explosives.
We need to ration.
Ration my ass.
Didn't you see how they jump?
We blow up all the trails
around the building.
But someone always remembers
them, so they reappear again.
In order to stop the Reapers,
we always have to be
on high alert.
We take turns keeping watch.
Yan says there's a whole island
here in Coma free of Reapers.
We're always looking for those
who can help us get there.
He's very certain about you
for some reason.
You need to eat
and drink here.
Hunger and cold
are all memories
but everything is like
in reality,
so we have to go outside.
Those from the squad with
abilities are sent there.
- I don't remember my name.
- Nobody does.
By the way,
give yourself a nickname
before somebody else does.
- It's just a dream.
- Let's go.
To wake up,
it's just a room...
Hey!
Someone just died
to save you.
You can't wake up.
Do you understand?
Your body is in a coma
somewhere. You're here.
There's nothing you
can do about it.
And what is that?
Dreams.
They materialize
while we're asleep.
This way we can remember
something from reality.
You'll get used to it.
Gnome lives there,
Tank, then Spirit,
Astronomer, me and Phantom.
The rest live downstairs.
You'll receive clothes
and ammo from Tank.
You and Phantom
are together?
What?
It's empty.
Spend a couple of weeks here
and it'll start to take shape.
It's yours.
Go inside.
Usually a newcomer
goes through an initiation.
But Yan decided to put you here
with the squad right away.
Ah, the man from the balcony.
Is he a leader of some sort?
He's been living here
longer than anybody else.
He's left Coma once.
That's why we know
what this world is like.
He taught us how
to survive here.
We owe him our lives.
Including you.
Ok, get some rest.
We'll see what you're
made of tomorrow.
And Phantom and I
are not together.
- I didn't mean to...
- Even though he thinks we are.
That's not how it is.
Wow!
Looks like you really
are a phenomenon.
Don't even think
of going there.
Dreams are tricky.
You can get lost.
You won't be able
to get out of there.
So, how are you?
Are you settling in ok?
- I guess so.
- Don't bullshit me.
Everyone goes crazy
at first in here.
Listen, I was a little hard
on you back there.
- No hard feelings, ok?
- Yeah, all good.
Peace?
Peace.
You see,
Yan is trying to
find this island of his.
Points out to some
chosen ones.
It's not my business really.
I'm not against it.
I have people to take care of.
The discipline, subordination...
I understand.
Got it.
Good man.
I liked you from the start.
You're smarter
than the others.
So stay away from my girl.
I like her.
She's acting out.
But that's ok.
We're almost there.
Well, I wouldn't say that.
Yan might see
something in you.
But he's made
mistakes in the past.
And again,
I lead the squad.
Not him.
We're supposed to be friends,
and you're rude.
No, I just wanted to say that
she should decide for herself.
You haven't figured
shit out yet.
- Stand up.
- What for?
Stand up, soldier!
Chop-chop!
Everyone's tired
of waiting for you.
Some people develop unique
abilities here in Coma.
It all depends on
their way of thinking
and predisposition.
Spirit, for instance,
senses Reapers from afar
and invokes ghosts.
Astronomer draws the routes.
Pilot can locate
real people in Coma.
In order to discover
those abilities,
a person needs a push.
Needs to be put in danger.
Let's see why you
are so special.
Gnome, launch a half!
Hey!
Get it together!
Do something!
So far so bad.
But you know,
often the abilities...
...flourish in real combat.
There, outside.
That's how it happened to me,
for instance.
But we aren't animals who put
you in real combat right away.
Gnome has built me...
...a training machine.
Bring out your dummy,
Gnome!
I said, bring it out.
It's the enemy!
Attack!
Fight!
You can do it!
So you can't act
on anything?
What did you do for a living?
I was an architect,
I think.
Cable!
Take the rookie.
We've never had
an architect.
Afternoon shift!
Wake up!
Get to work!
Higher!
Ok, secure it!
Cable!
We're going to your submarine
to get the explosives.
Seems like we've cleared up
everything here.
Get ready.
Yes, Commander!
Keep working, Architect.
We don't need freeloaders.
Hey.
Stop sitting around!
Who's going to work?
Why are you upset?
You should be happy, you fool.
You're lucky!
And why am I lucky?
You may not have these
valuable super powers, so what?
Look, there are plenty of us
who didn't pass the test.
We were mistakenly picked.
At least we don't
have to go out there.
You'll be safer!
So live your life!
And you will come out of the
coma and continue on your path.
But you will have to wait
for a while.
Time flows differently here.
We're not entirely sure,
but it seems like...
...it's no less than 1 to 100.
One day in reality is equal
to several months in Coma.
I've been here
for 15 years,
but you can live here
for thousands.
The question is,
how do you want
to spend these thousand years?
You saved me.
Tell me what my purpose is here?
It doesn't matter.
Who you want to be
is for you to decide.
You can move hardware
all your life
or you can develop
your abilities...
But sometimes...
Sometimes it's hard to recognize
them in the beginning.
A person can feel like
he can do something
and then nothing
comes out of it.
I think I finished
a building in town,
but I don't know how.
I tried to build something here
but it didn't work out.
Phantom wasn't lying.
Abilities can develop out there.
We don't put the newbies
out there, too risky.
But it's a personal choice.
In his case...
...it worked:
superhuman strength, speed.
He became a leader here.
I've seen a lot of people
come through here
and I think we're here
for a reason.
Everyone who's here
didn't make it in reality.
They didn't have
a future there.
I don't remember
anything about myself.
Just some fragments
of memories.
Maybe that's for the best.
In which way?
Without the heavy burden
of memories,
we can have a fresh start.
Nobody will tell you
who you are but yourself.
This world is made
of our thoughts.
- The rules are slightly different here.
- Grip it firmly.
And here, unlike reality,
one can achieve
whatever one wants.
But that doesn't mean that
you should do nothing.
The sight doesn't shift
anywhere. Got it?
- Yeah.
- Get your palm closer to you.
What do you want?
I'm going with you.
What?
You want to join us?
Take the rookie.
What the fuck for?
Because I said so.
He'll get killed.
So be it. We have enough
people to move hardware.
So look...
I got it, thanks.
Astronomer...
Excuse me,
can somebody give me a gun?
There's Gnome's tunnel.
We turn there.
Yes!
There's my tunnel.
I'm sorry,
but why is it "Gnome's tunnel"?
Because I remember it.
And I remember that beauty
that we're on our way to see.
This world is made up
of memories.
Sometimes it can be easy to
figure out who they belong to.
Astronomer has this
whole theory about it.
Ask him.
It's nuts!
Tell us, Astronomer.
- I heard you have a lot of them?
- Dreams?
- Yeah, in your room.
- Well, yeah.
The coma separates
consciousness and body.
We lose our memories here.
We lose ourselves.
Get it?
- So?
- But our dreams
hold all the information about
what we've remembered
during life.
Even this place, where we
are now, exists there.
You can find yourself
dreaming there.
Ah, so that way you can
come out of the coma?
What are you talking about?
Yan told you.
Anyone who tries to enter
the dreams won't make it.
- What's so hard to get?
- Doesn't mean it's impossible.
Did anyone
ask your opinion?
Reapers!
Nah, nah, nah.
It's safe.
It's a two-day
detour from there.
- Can they see us?
- They sense us.
We emit a signal,
a frequency.
- That's why I made the whistle.
- What whistle?
Just in case,
so we don't all blow up.
- Only one of us.
- Like Pilot.
You switch on the whistle
and it attracts the Reapers.
Then you blow yourself up
with dynamite.
If this world is made
of memories,
how did they get here?
Through us.
How?
Coma patients.
Their brain is dead
but life support is still on.
The relatives are
against turning it off.
The dead brain creates them.
They die...
...and decay all the time.
But they have the ability
to turn the living into
the same black shit
they are made of.
I'd rather be taken off the
machine than end up like that.
Enough of that!
Let's go!
There's our main attraction!
Architect,
did you bring spare underwear?
Yeah, they're trigger-happy
with their guns.
- Who?
- The guards.
- Memories.
- Why would they shoot us?
They shoot at strangers.
That's how I remembered it.
Ok, take this.
Turn this and
it'll enhance your bio-signal.
It'll attract the Reapers,
like bees to honey.
- Got it.
- Don't worry.
There are no Reapers here.
But don't start shooting
for no reason.
You're so boring,
Astronomer.
We run a greater risk
of dying from boredom
than from the Reapers.
Enough chewing the fat!
I'm leading.
Tank, stay behind and cover me.
Spirit, distract them.
The rest of you reserves,
stay in the back
for your own safety.
Any questions?
No questions.
Let's go!
Freeze!
Did you work here?
What is this place?
A lot of factories
are mixed up in here.
Combined memories
of many people.
There!
There's the hangar!
I remember now!
There's a secret door.
They will leave now.
We have 30 seconds
to get there.
Not yet, Phantom!
Phantom!
Come on!
- Come on!
- Freeze!
Tank, throw a grenade!
- It's too far, I won't make it!
- You'll make it! Throw it!
Tank!
Cover me!
Stay back, Tank!
Whoo-hoo!
Get down!
Spirit!
Here...
Uh-huh.
What the hell was that!
You're going to get
us all killed!
What the hell do you know?
- Relax!
- We've summoned the Reapers here!
- Spirit?
- I can't sense them yet.
See?
No one's gonna hurt you.
If you ever shout
at me again,
I will break you in half.
I'm in charge here!
Do you disagree?
I can't hear you!
Yes!
Got it!
You ok?
I definitely don't
recall that.
Each of those torpedoes
has explosives.
That will last
for a month.
Get to work.
On it!
Come on, come on!
Come on!
Easy, easy!
Easy!
Slowly up!
Come on, come on!
Let me heal it.
It's nothing.
Come on.
I'll check your hand as well.
I said it's nothing!
Thanks.
Careful!
Hold it tighter!
Just a slight knock
and it'll blow everything up!
Fucking Coma!
I recognize this.
It's some country...
...but I can't remember which.
What's up?
Everything is like
a dream here, right?
A dream.
You think you can grasp it...
- Reapers!
- I told you so.
How far?
- About a third of a mile!
- Get it down!
I can't!
One more minute!
- Get down!
- I said one minute!
Freaking commander!
- I'll finish it myself.
- Ok.
He won't make it.
Are you happy now?
Hold it for as long as
you can, buddy. Got it?
Gnome stays here,
the rest follow me!
- He can't get it down by himself!
- Cable is up there!
No discussions,
obey the order!
On three. One, two,
three. Run!
Stop! Hold it!
I said hold it!
Run!
Come back!
- Come on!
- Come back!
Everyone come back!
Fucker!
Don't you dare!
Move it to the exit.
Hurry!
So then I look,
you guys are running,
the stupid thing starts to slide
down, dragging me with it.
As I'm riding it,
I'm thinking, "This is it."
But then the sparks,
this ramp... Boom!
My first thought was,
"I'm dead, it exploded."
Who the hell knows how you trip
out while dying in a coma?
Architect, you fool!
Why didn't you run like the
rest? It was an order.
That makes me think...
That means you can build a wall
where necessary during combat?
Yes.
And maybe a bridge
of sorts?
I guess a bridge as well.
Attaboy!
You will be useful
for the unit, Architect.
We'll get to places
we didn't dare think of before.
And I'm thinking...
...there's a better way
to use his abilities.
We've been looking
for a hiding place
from the Reapers
for a long time.
An isolated place.
But we couldn't, because people
not only remember a place,
but how they got there,
as well.
Isn't that right,
Astronomer?
But what if the place
wasn't created from memory,
but rather from imagination.
If it's created,
designed like that ramp
on which Cable fell,
then it isn't intertwined
with other memories.
And therefore safe.
I told you,
I will bring you to the island.
And he will build it for us.
You think he can do it?
A whole island?
Can you?
Um...
Yes, I can.
The best time to deploy
is right now.
Yan, don't you want to
run it by me first?
- We need time to prepare.
- What do you say, Astronomer?
If we're deploying
along with the civilians,
then we need to pick
the safest route.
- We haven't had one in a long time.
- Hey, theorist!
- It's all on paper, Yan.
- Didn't we...
...clear all the explosives
in the area?
Where will we go
when we run out?
Sooner or later Reapers will
see the people through the bus.
What then?
We leave tomorrow.
Astronomer will lead
the squad.
Yan...
Yan, I might've
overstepped today, but...
You were reckless.
Attracted the Reapers.
That wasn't the agreement.
It's my place!
This mission is way
too important.
Important mission?
Maybe they deserve
to know something more?
We will talk later!
Why aren't we drinking, huh?
Tomorrow is a big day.
Right, Architect?
Damn it!
What are you doing?
Shit, you scared me.
Nothing, just trying something.
Trying to build?
Well yeah, trying.
Can I watch?
I'm almost done, actually.
It's not working out?
No, not at all.
Why did you tell everyone
you'll build that island?
Back at the submarine
you called everyone back.
You weren't sure
it would work.
You could've killed everyone.
But it worked.
You've gotten by
so far without me...
Just figure out
what went wrong.
Wait!
You were concentrated.
You did something with your
hands and something appeared.
Yes, and the ramp appeared.
Why are you saying that now?
No, the blueprint appeared.
Appeared...
The blueprint appeared...
Yes, I need to imagine
the full blueprint.
The full blueprint...
So, which city should I build
for you on my island?
They say you have a lot
of memories in your room.
Well, yeah.
I want to see them.
Will you show me?
How many there are!
I've got almost none.
Meaning you don't
remember anything at all?
Only a feeling.
Did you get into
a car accident?
Yes, I was on my way
to an important meeting,
but it turned out
to be a trap.
An architect trap?
Yeah, I agree,
it sounds crazy.
And this woman?
Were you close?
I don't remember,
and it's not important
anymore. I...
- My life is here now.
- But you wanted to wake up so much.
Yes, yes, I know. But...
I met you and I can
become myself here.
I feel that Yan is right.
If we don't remember anything,
we can start a life over.
And become someone who
we've always wanted to be.
- Sounds silly, right?
- No.
I feel the same way.
Then you remember
something.
I do.
I couldn't be with
the one I wanted.
And here I can.
During the mission,
everyone should strictly
follow the leader.
Don't deviate,
keep your distance.
- Will we get guns?
- You don't need guns.
There are no Reapers
on that route.
This is where
we'll build an island.
We will go through the hills.
They won't even notice us.
What if you missed
some of them?
I know them all.
I've considered each one.
Spirit?
Seems about right.
Usually I sense them...
Phantom, listen.
Should we take these
fuse wires for the explosives?
Astronomer is leading
the squad.
He's the commander now.
Ok, got it.
So, I've got a question.
What should I build
on this island?
You're the architect,
so it's up to you.
I do have one project,
but it's not mine,
and the client would be
against me borrowing it.
Oh, I think you can
tell him to go to hell now.
- Well...
- I don't know what kind of project it is,
but you, Architect,
should build me a custom hut.
- With a garage, you know?
- And a hot tub for me!
- A shooting range for me!
- Ok, guys, chill! Let's form a line!
Reaper!
That's impossible.
I've checked everything!
Are you sure?
- I say what I sense.
- Damn it.
It's always like that
with the Reapers.
We won't make it far with
all this ballast, if at all!
Should we turn back?
We won't get another chance
to get there any time soon,
but it's up to you.
Phantom.
You've got more experience.
What do you think?
We should split up,
check all directions,
then return here
and choose a new route.
Reasonable.
Two of us should stay,
to protect the others.
- Architect and I will stay.
- Architect won't be able to help you.
He can't shoot,
has no experience.
You better stay with Tank.
- Or I'll stay if you like.
- No.
Nothing will happen to him!
We're just scouting,
but we have civilians here.
No!
I can do it.
It's ok.
Tank stays here.
Architect, get to that hill.
When you see a plane, come
back right away. Understood?
The rest go in your
respective direction.
Spread out!
Tank, what are you
doing here?
Yan sent me,
like he sensed it.
Hurry!
Reapers!
About a thousand feet!
We need to leave!
- What...
- Give me that!
- What are you doing?
- I said give it to me!
Let go of it!
Let him go!
Where did you get that?
- You planted it!
- You set us all up!
I didn't mean to.
We need to leave.
Hey! Wait!
It's not what you think.
You don't know everything.
It's... He's the one who...
We need to leave.
We all need to leave right now.
Reapers!
Astronomer!
Lead everyone away!
Listen up everyone!
Get rid of the heavy gear!
Cable!
On your right!
Architect, to the bus!
Hurry!
Astronomer,
take him with you!
Hey.
Hey!
- They responded to the Reaper whistle.
- Behind you!
This is it, guys.
There!
Architect!
We're almost there.
- Were you given an advance payment?
- What advance payment?
Don't you see?
Unlike other idiots,
they accepted me
and my projects!
Yeah, right.
They told you how cool you are,
how great your projects
are and that's it?
Have you lost your mind?
Do you watch TV?
Do you have any idea what
they say about your clients?
They are using you.
They won't pay you.
Or even worse,
I don't know.
There is a way out.
The Teacher loves you.
Save us!
Follow his calling.
- Read what the Teacher says about you!
- Damn!
A path to a new life
will open up for you!
A new life awaits.
Read what the Teacher
says about you.
He will set you free.
- Is that him?
- I don't know.
You don't know
what he looks like?
We just talked online,
that's it.
Zip it!
We were told
you'd be alone.
- But he's not alone!
- Calm down.
We can only let
you in alone.
My apologies,
we have very strict rules.
- Are you the client?
- Oh no, of course not.
I'm just a simple assistant.
It was me who sent
you the proposal mail.
The Teacher is
awaiting you inside.
- You aren't going to...
- I beg you, please wait for me here.
- Hold on.
- What?
Here, take it.
What is it?
A hospital?
Used to be.
We just took it over.
Genius. How long have
you had this idea?
Since university.
And people continue
building these ugly boxes.
Yes, you're absolutely right,
it's crazy.
I've sent them to many places.
To different competitions etc...
Pointless. It's pointless
to cast pearls before swine.
This world will never
recognize something unique,
even if it's 100 times better.
Would you really be able
to build what I propose?
Follow me,
I'll show you something.
Pardon me, what exactly
does your organization do?
You know,
there are many rumors.
We give people an
enlightened new life.
You can see it on the billboard.
You'll see it for yourself.
While studying the cerebral
physiology of the brain,
I discovered that in a state
of a deep coma,
one has access to a whole world
that no one else knows about.
This world is much better
than the common reality.
Do you mean dreams?
It's impossible to explain.
Would you like to take a look?
I'm in a hurry,
I've got things to do.
It won't take long.
I'm sure you'll like it!
Get off!
Stay away!
- What happened?
- Come on! Go! Go! Go!
I just ran a person over!
- Drive! Drive! Drive!
- I told you they were lying!
Why don't you listen to me!
Why can't you ever listen to me!
She was put in a coma just
a couple of hours before you.
But there,
months have passed.
Extraordinary, isn't it?
Who the hell are you?
A group of scientists who want
to gift people a new world.
And the spiritual teachings?
To help to finance
the project.
My studies were deemed a
failure, so I had to find a way.
As a wise man said,
"If you want to get rich,
create your own religion."
You know, by the way, it was
much easier than I thought.
- So my city project is a lie?
- Of course not!
The city is real.
I've formed a team of people
with specific brain pathologies,
so they could survive
in a coma.
I found an artist with an
amazing memory and imagination,
so he could work on a worthy
project and realize it there.
What for?
Don't you get it?
To live there.
In dreams?
The coma world was known
to people long before us.
Ancient rulers of many
cultures went there.
But modern technology
plastered it
with walking corpses
of Reapers.
And all these people found a
new meaning there, a new life.
Even you were
almost happy there.
There, you are
the great architect.
And what awaits you here?
Custom cottages.
If you're lucky.
Did they get the
same injection as me?
It's faster
and better for them.
Maybe you should have
asked them first!
You know, Phantom's memory
was fully recovered.
He remembered
how he got here
and who he was.
But he didn't want
to wake up.
Later a Reaper got to him.
On a physiological level
it's a necrosis of brain tissue.
He panicked,
started to threaten us that
he would reveal the truth.
In the end he killed
a bunch of people
and almost screwed up
everything.
It took some effort
to get you out of there.
So the more you know, really,
the more problems arise.
And... all of your followers,
will you take them
with you to Coma?
We need them to
create a mode of life.
Slaves.
But they don't know that they
will be put into a coma, right?
In return I give people an
infinite life full of meaning.
What's wrong with that?
Everyone gets what
they want in Coma.
One person is a commander
or spiritual leader,
another person
is a great architect.
You are crazy!
Don't you understand
these are just dreams?
It doesn't matter.
Look...
That's it,
I'm out of here.
Just let us go, please,
that's all.
Knowledge is the source
of all problems.
You will still accomplish
what is required.
I won't go back
there anymore.
You know,
when a Reaper gets a person,
their brain dies
in a couple of minutes.
Did you leave her
in a field?
Hmm, strange.
For now...
For now it seems normal.
But it's impossible to see
everything--
Enough!
Let her go!
She's not a part of this!
I invited you alone.
You started the race
and crashed.
You did this to yourself,
and to her.
Either way, you're building the
island and your city on it.
Then I will let you both go.
You will let all of us go!
I give you my word,
I won't hold anyone back.
You will wake up
in your home again.
The brain is drawn to
the strongest memories.
This time, your memory
will recover much faster.
You will find Astronomer.
The coordinates for building
the city are on his map.
What if I don't make it?
You will.
This stimulant will make
your brain work more intensely.
Sure, it will
damage your health,
but you'll be like
Superman for a while.
Wait, how will they know when
it's time to get out of Coma?
They won't.
Well, there is a way.
From within.
A back door of sorts.
I'll show you once you've
accomplished everything.
Think about it.
I was able to leave.
Sleep.
Get down!
That's it.
That's the last one.
Leave it with us.
Yeah...
It's not what you think.
We need to leave.
Hurry.
A lot of people resist it
in the beginning.
Maybe you should
give him some more time.
No.
Do as I say.
Here it is.
Yan chose this place himself.
He said it was majestic.
What's wrong?
Are you hurt?
It's nothing.
I'm just tired.
I will live on this island
for some time.
Soon...
I can't believe it.
Yan was right after all.
Don't you get it?
We are all laying
in that lunatic's basement.
There will be no island!
It's just a dream!
I know it's hard
to comprehend,
but when you see it
with your own eyes,
how you're laying there...
So you told them after all.
They've been through
so much already.
It's not very fair.
Where do you want it?
The bridge should
start right here.
"God saw all
that he had made,
and it was very good."
What do you need reality
for after this?
Yan, I've built everything.
Let us go.
Spirit.
In life you saw dead people
all around you...
...and had seizures
a couple of times a day.
You don't have any relatives,
and you lost your only child.
I saved you from the asylum,
where you would have rotted
till your dying day.
Tank.
You lost your family
in an accident.
Became a raging alcoholic.
Started shooting
at your neighbors.
You would have ended up
in a madhouse or a jail.
Astronomer, you're autistic.
You can't even leave
your house.
Your poor old folks.
What will happen
when they die, huh?
And you have a more serious
issue, Architect.
Your ideas are beautiful,
but way ahead of their time,
so no one wants them.
Everyone has abandoned you,
including her,
who was by your side
till the very end.
He is nothing out there.
An infantile,
unrecognized genius
who lets all his anger
out on you,
on the whole world.
I bet you contemplated suicide
long before you got that email.
This project gave
new meaning to your life.
- Were you given an advance payment?
- What advance?
Don't you see?
Unlike other idiots,
they accepted me
and my projects!
Keep laughing.
Everything will change for us
after this, I know it.
For us?
There is no "us".
That's why you're
sitting in this car.
Jesus!
They told you
how cool you are,
how great your projects are,
and that's it?
- Have you lost your mind?
- You used to believe in me.
They are using you,
they won't pay you.
- Or even worse, I don't know.
- Got a guilty conscience?
This is a great car.
I'm sure it was a gift,
considering you're just a nurse.
But that's ok.
I'll buy you a new one
when I'm famous.
This is the last time
I'm helping you.
We're staying.
Stay.
But now
I won't let you stay.
I can't.
You would reveal everything.
- And who's going to believe us?
- My followers.
You can't hide it forever.
And in heaven,
there is no place for those who
know the secret of its creation.
It concerns you as well.
Now that you know everything,
I can't let you live
among the others.
We won't tell anyone.
It's done.
You are suffocating there.
Brain oxygen
starvation has started
and you will feel it soon.
I don't know in which order
you were switched off.
There, it's a matter
of seconds,
but here we've got
about fifteen minutes
to say our goodbyes.
Stop!
I was prepared for this.
Brain stimulation
can be harmful,
but I thought it wouldn't
hurt in this situation.
I have business to attend to.
Damn it!
You warned me that
they would fuck me over.
- What?
- We need to wake up.
We will wake up
and switch him off.
The back door!
Astronomer!
How did he escape
when the Reapers attacked?
Dreams.
All of us are dreaming
where we are laying right now.
If you can find yourself
in that dream, then...
That's why he said that
dreams are dangerous!
- They are dangerous.
- Let's go!
- It's not that easy!
- We don't have much time, Astronomer!
Spirit, let's go!
Come on.
Astronomer, we need
to get to Yan's room. Hurry!
They are already there.
- We won't make it!
- Shit!
I've got an idea.
Come on!
Hurry!
- What?
- It's not how I remember it.
These are dreams,
I told you.
We need to try harder
to find that place.
Everything is mixed up here.
Then there, I think.
There was a door and stairs.
It's not the same!
Astronomer?
Everything is linked
by association in here.
Try not to search according
to the blueprint of the rooms.
How?
Details!
Search for a detail that
reminds you of that room.
A detail...
Yes, here it is.
It was in a painting
in that room!
Right.
I was right.
Of course you're right.
Astronomer is a genius
after all.
Where would we be
without him?
Our memory retains the things
we find most interesting.
And of all things,
you remembered a temple
in a painting.
A true architect.
You know, I really hoped
you'd be smarter than the rest.
You reminded me of myself
when I was young.
Medicine fights to prolong
a human's life
for five more years.
But I was able to
prolong it for a thousand.
And you know what?
My department was closed,
to finance the development
of a new anti-cellulite product.
And I never understood how to
live in a world so foolish,
so ugly.
But then I realized
there is another world.
I discovered it.
Fly, run!
But just like you,
I had my doubts.
It's just an illusion
after all.
I thought so,
until I made a discovery.
Everything that we live for,
all of our emotions--
joy, happiness, anger,
astonishment, sadness--
they are all simply
electrical signals of our brain.
We measured them on people
in a coma and in real life,
and you know what?
They are absolutely identical.
Life in Coma
is as real as it gets.
That's it.
It's as simple as that.
We found it, Fly.
Come on.
Quiet.
Breath.
Breath. Quiet.
What...
We're going home.
Everything is going
to be alright.
We're going home.
We're going.
Stand up.
Well, I'm almost done,
but I need a break.
- Let's take Torik out for a walk.
- Alright, let's go.
What about your projects?
Did anyone reply?
No.
Maybe that's down
to the presentation.
No, everything is fine.
You just have to be realistic.
My projects are worthless.
But at least this year
will be better financially.
We won the contract.
- Are you kidding?
- No.
Congratulations.
It looks like
the scandal involving
the Foundation
of Eternal Life
will end without a result,
after all.
All charges will be dropped
due to a lack of evidence,
as it was established that
all subjects of the experiment
were there legally.
The organization continues
to successfully
recruit followers...
Do you think they
will come for us?
We have nothing
to be afraid of.
Get dressed.
By the way,
the mail came this morning.
There was an envelope
for you.
- Yeah, I saw it already.
- What was in it?
Nothing special.
Just some documents
for an old project.
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org